A Guide to the James Branch Cabell Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #5491
James Branch Cabell Collection 1922-1932
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
5491
39 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift 1956 Nov 20
Item Listing
- Letters
  - James Branch Cabell to [ T. Gilbert Porterfield], 1922 Jul 11; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1922 Jul 12; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - George W. Warren to T/ Gilbert Porterfield, 1922 Jul 13; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1922 Jul 14; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to George Warren, 1922 Jul 15; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to [Mason] Lowance, 1922 Aug 30; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1923 Jun 21; TLS, 1 p.
  - [T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1923 Jun 23; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1923 Jun 25; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1923 Jun 26; TL, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1923 Jun 28; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1923 Jun 29; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to [Lyman] Denison, 1923 Sep 10; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1924 Jun 7; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1924 Jun 11; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1924 Jun 18; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1924 Jun 20; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to Mason [Lowance], 1924 Sep 5; TLS, 1 p.
  - Mason Lowance to James Branch Cabell, 1924 Sep 6 & 7; TL, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1925 May 30; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1925 Jun 6; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1925 Jun 8; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1925 Jun 9; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1925 Jun 24; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1926 Apr 24; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1926 Apr 26; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1926 Sep 9; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1926 Sep 13; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to [Lyman] Denison, 1927 May 19; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Lyman Denison, 1927 May 26; TLS, 1 p.
  - T. Gilbert Porterfield to James Branch Cabell, 1931 May 14; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1931 May 18; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1931 May 19; TLS, 1 p.
  - T. Gilbert Porterfield to James Branch Cabell, 1931 May 21; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1931 May 23; TLS, 1 p.
  - T. Gilbert Porterfield to James Branch Cabell, 1931 May 27; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1931 Jun 24; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1931 Jun 25; TL, 1 p. [carbon]
  - James Branch Cabell to T. Gilbert Porterfield, 1932 Mar 4; TLS, 1 p.
  - [ T. Gilbert Porterfield] to James Branch Cabell, 1932 Mar 14; TL, 1 p. [carbon]